{
    "id": "9bb31d08901b4b3089dadf67374fdaa5",
    "title": "Subordinating Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………. she was ill, I went without her.",
            "description": "As gives the reason. For is a coordinating conjunction. It cannot start a sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef14e3c1d17347b581d051fe6332c116"
        },
        {
            "question": "I said nothing ………………………… he was angry.",
            "description": "Because shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "because",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "245783b8eab74ad282414af38cbdf8da"
        },
        {
            "question": "You won’t lose weight ………………………… you cut down on fatty foods.",
            "description": "Unless means if not. You won't lose weight if you do not cut down on fatty foods. Or You won't lose weight unless you cut down on fatty foods.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "in case"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "deb5dc9de72f4060bd053f53b01c414e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He smiled ………………………….. he knew everything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d0590f75e206463d9960c9885014e06d"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. it was late, we decided to go out.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b6f42f3923c497684e778e7320295e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will go …………………………. you forbid me.",
            "description": "Even if refers to present or future. ",
            "answers": [
                "even if",
                "if",
                "even",
                "even though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e9313f84f62494dbbc5b81a3f7315b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… you were playing, she was studying for her exam.",
            "description": "Either when or while is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "Since",
                "When"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "944f335cbdaa450d9c6dcd1f6f14e0ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "The birds flew away ………………………… the hunter raised his gun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "as long as",
                "no sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3b51795ebd9c4177b66b8e890180a5f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can stay with me ……………………….. you take care of your expenses.",
            "description": "Either as long as or if is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "as long as",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bfd63fb8d2ac48fea61afd2a2dd95e4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. they fought bravely, they could not beat the enemy.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. Even if refers to future.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3390f564fa5342fc9bf897087a5ebd82"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. had I reached home, ………………………… trouble started brewing.",
            "description": "The correct expression is hardly...when...",
            "answers": [
                "Hardly, when",
                "No sooner, when",
                "Hardly, than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "150f0e2d077e4e928be3bab14aa20404"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… you needed help, you could call me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cbe4b415883e4cb993bf5dd22a5ebb92"
        }
    ]
}